Sure, sure you can shower here there's plenty of warm water.
I have a boiler (spelled like "uncle") that fixes people!
OK sista', I'll get back to you.
I have a suit at the door.
Bye.
A minute of your time?
Do you wanna drink somethin' man?
As you most certainly have heard, under auxiliary legislation
"Databases, Data Fidelity, Entry & Transfer Act (2009)"
in accordance with the legal precedent "The State vs Blake Doe",
on failure of numeric estimation for a citizen's date of expiry
the erroneous record is to be ammended immediately
by verbatim realization of the datum, ex post facto.
Yeah, yeah, of course...
In our systems you're listed as dead.
Awesome...
While clearly, you're alive.
I'm here to amend the mistake.
Cool.
Sign this form please.
Whoa, you're a pro...
Are you goin' through Petah Tikva?
No, I'm on my way to Tel-Aviv.
Great, I need to get to Ramat Gan.
Okay...
I'm Michael Farrera, Mike.
Shany, nice to meet you.
I think I lost them.
They put thoughts in your mind and make you do stuff.
They know I know things.
I know they killed my uncle!
And you know why?
They had an error in the computer, it said he was dead.
So instead of fixing the error they decided to kill him!
They even made him sign a form, 203D!
203D!
Stop!
I'll get off here, I don't like being predictable.
Shany?
Oded Schwartz, Vice President of the Data Fidelity Dept.
in the Census Bureau, glad to meet you.
on failure of numeric estimation for a citizen's date of expiry
the erroneous record is to be ammended immediately
by verbatim realization of the datum, ex post facto.
I didn't completely understand that...
Never Mind.
It's bureaucratic, that's my job.
So what...
what if I won't sign?
Then I'd have to request a signature from relatives
Retroactively.
Hi, it's Oded. Schwartz.
Requesting permission to use
two additional bullets.
Yes.
Yes, I signed.
Of course I'll fill in Form-55!
Thanks.
Oded Schwartz, Vice President of the Data Fidelity Dept.
in the Census Bureau, glad to meet you.
Have you seen a young woman around here?
No, why do you ask?
I... need her to sign a form.
She's not here.
He's gone.
You can leave by the back door.
Oded Schwartz, I believe we've met.
Hello.
Oded again.
Requesting permission to work overtime.
Is it approved?
I see.
OK.
We'll have to continue this tomorrow.